<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How will this affect the school? on Information on the railyard for Creekside</title>
    <link>/about/railyard-features/noise/how/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How will this affect the school? on Information on the railyard for Creekside</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/about/railyard-features/noise/how/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Screening distances</title>
      <link>/about/railyard-features/noise/how/distance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/railyard-features/noise/how/distance/</guid>
      <description>Guidelines for evaluating the noise impact of a maintenance facility near a school may specify certain screening distances to select schools, but they are &amp;lsquo;NOT a substitute for case- and site-specific evaluation of potential risks and hazards&amp;rsquo;. These distances may not be a good predictor of an environmental hazard.
 Federal Transportation Administration (FTA) guidelines mention
 that &amp;lsquo;a maintenance facility near a school&amp;rsquo; (p. 33) is one location recommended for a &amp;lsquo;Detailed Noise Analysis&amp;rsquo;  The &amp;lsquo;screening distance for noise assessments&amp;rsquo; at a school is  1,000 feet for unobstructed distances 650 feet for obstructed distances (&amp;lsquo;with intervening buildings&amp;rsquo;)    According to the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) school siting guidelines</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Locations</title>
      <link>/about/railyard-features/noise/how/monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/railyard-features/noise/how/monitor/</guid>
      <description>GoTriangle estimated noise levels for areas near the railyard operations maintenance facility site based on long term noise monitoring sites nowhere near the ROMF site, west of I-40.  Closest long-term noise monitoring sites closest to Creekside and west of I-40 were:  214 Celeste Circle, Chapel Hill (LT-4) 4315 Randall Road, Durham (LT-5)    Annotated map of noise monitoring sites from noise report</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>