<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Information on the rail yard for Creekside</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Information on the rail yard for Creekside</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 08:57:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive version</title>
      <link>/timeline/timelinejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timeline/timelinejs/</guid>
      <description> A timeline of events leading up to the ROMF/railyard site approval. At each of the time points below, there was no effort by GoTriangle, Durham City, Durham County or Creekside Elementary administration to directly contact or inform parents, guardians or teaching staff at Creekside Elementary.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARCS</title>
      <link>/action/arcs-nc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/action/arcs-nc/</guid>
      <description>Advocates for residential communities and and schools (ARCS) is a policy group that supports sensible growth. Their action page has useful information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tick Tock</title>
      <link>/timeline/texttimeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timeline/texttimeline/</guid>
      <description>Date Topic Detail Any direct contact of Creekside parents by the school district?     2010-2012 Site identification Go Triangle Alternatives Analysis identified 5 sites for the ROMF No   May-12 Public comment period After four meetings, GoTriangle identified fifth Alston Ave site No   2012 Public comment period Hundreds of comments opposing the Cornwallis Road site proposed for ROMF/rail yard No   2012 Environmental Analysis Process GoTriangle hosted more than 300 meetings with public groups No   6/24/2015      7/25/2015 GoTriangle notified Durham Public School District and Creekside administration GoTriangle notified Durham Public School District about proposed ROMF at Farrington Road site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>newsletter</title>
      <link>/action/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/action/newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Keep updated by subscribing to a monthly update via email regarding upcoming events around Creekside Elementary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA statement</title>
      <link>/pta/statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pta/statement/</guid>
      <description>Statement on Rail Operations Maintenance Facility The Creekside PTA expresses its concern about the potential negative impacts of a Rail Operations Maintenance Facility (ROMF) in such close proximity to a school, as well as the lack of substantive communication with the school community during the planning process.
The Creekside PTA calls upon local leaders to immediately identify representatives to join a formal body that will work together to resolve concerns around potential impacts on student safety and quality of the learning environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA information sheet</title>
      <link>/pta/infosheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pta/infosheet/</guid>
      <description>General information about the ROMF facility distributed at the Feburary 2018 meeting  All light rail trains will be stored, tested, and maintained at this location. This is not a light rail station, it is an industrial railyard maintenance facility. The ROMF will operate 24&amp;frasl;7. Creekside Elementary is approximately 350 yards from the proposed site. According to a mapping evaluation conducted by parents, Creekside Elementary will be closer to a ROMF than any other school in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>presentation</title>
      <link>/pta/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pta/presentation/</guid>
      <description>Presentation February 4, 2018 PTA Advocacy Committee presentation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>