<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Information on the railyard for Creekside</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Information on the railyard for Creekside</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 08:57:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>/about/maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/maps/</guid>
      <description>This railyard maintenance facility is planned for an industrial site at the intersection of Ephesus Church and Farrington Roads, less than 0.25 miles away from Creekside Elementary.
 On December 3, 2018, the Durham City Council approved an industrial rezoning for this location. The nearest industrial zone in Durham is over 4 miles away in Research Triangle Park.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Locations</title>
      <link>/about/railyard-features/noise/how/monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/railyard-features/noise/how/monitor/</guid>
      <description>GoTriangle estimated noise levels for areas near the railyard operations maintenance facility site based on long term noise monitoring sites nowhere near the ROMF site, west of I-40.  Closest long-term noise monitoring sites closest to Creekside and west of I-40 were:  214 Celeste Circle, Chapel Hill (LT-4) 4315 Randall Road, Durham (LT-5)    Annotated map of noise monitoring sites from noise report</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tick Tock</title>
      <link>/timeline/ticktock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timeline/ticktock/</guid>
      <description>From 2012 to 2018, the school district, GoTriangle and the City/County government sytematically failed to inform parents and guardians at Creekside Elementary of the public zoning hearings and public comment periods for the rail yard site selection. As a result, almost all people with children at Creekside Elementary did not have a chance to participate in the site selection process.
   Date Topic Detail Any direct contact of Creekside parents by the school district or GoTriangle?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARCS</title>
      <link>/action/arcs-nc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/action/arcs-nc/</guid>
      <description>Advocates for residential communities and and schools (ARCS) is a local policy group that supports sensible growth. Their action page has useful information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive version</title>
      <link>/timeline/timelinejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/timeline/timelinejs/</guid>
      <description> A timeline of events leading up to the ROMF/railyard site approval. At each of the time points below, there was no effort by GoTriangle, Durham City, Durham County or Creekside Elementary administration to directly contact or inform parents, guardians or teaching staff at Creekside Elementary.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>newsletter</title>
      <link>/action/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/action/newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Subscribe to a newsletter to learn the latest on any development activity occuring around Creekside Elementary.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA February 2018 statement</title>
      <link>/pta/statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pta/statement/</guid>
      <description>Statement on Rail Operations Maintenance Facility The Creekside PTA expresses its concern about the potential negative impacts of a Rail Operations Maintenance Facility (ROMF) in such close proximity to a school, as well as the lack of substantive communication with the school community during the planning process.
The Creekside PTA calls upon local leaders to immediately identify representatives to join a formal body that will work together to resolve concerns around potential impacts on student safety and quality of the learning environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA information sheet</title>
      <link>/pta/infosheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pta/infosheet/</guid>
      <description>General information about the ROMF facility distributed at the Feburary 2018 meeting  All light rail trains will be stored, tested, and maintained at this location. This is not a light rail station, it is an industrial railyard maintenance facility. The ROMF will operate 24&amp;frasl;7. Creekside Elementary is approximately 350 yards from the proposed site. According to a mapping evaluation conducted by parents, Creekside Elementary will be closer to a ROMF than any other school in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February presentation to parents</title>
      <link>/pta/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pta/presentation/</guid>
      <description>February 4, 2018 PTA Advocacy Committee presentation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>