<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PTA activity on We care about Creekside</title>
    <link>https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PTA activity on We care about Creekside</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA February 2018 statement</title>
      <link>https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/statement/</guid>
      <description>Statement on Rail Operations Maintenance Facility The Creekside PTA expresses its concern about the potential negative impacts of a Rail Operations Maintenance Facility (ROMF) in such close proximity to a school, as well as the lack of substantive communication with the school community during the planning process.
The Creekside PTA calls upon local leaders to immediately identify representatives to join a formal body that will work together to resolve concerns around potential impacts on student safety and quality of the learning environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PTA information sheet</title>
      <link>https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/infosheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/infosheet/</guid>
      <description>General information about the ROMF facility distributed at the Feburary 2018 meeting  All light rail trains will be stored, tested, and maintained at this location. This is not a light rail station, it is an industrial railyard maintenance facility. The ROMF will operate 24&amp;frasl;7. Creekside Elementary is approximately 350 yards from the proposed site. According to a mapping evaluation conducted by parents, Creekside Elementary will be closer to a ROMF than any other school in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February presentation to parents</title>
      <link>https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wecareaboutcreekside.com/pta/presentation/</guid>
      <description>February 4, 2018 PTA Advocacy Committee presentation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>